The President. The First Lady. The King. The Queen. The Mother. The Mistress...One
weekend would unite two great nations...After cocktails of course.
Hyde Park on Hudson is a comedy, drama, history film directed by Roger Michell.
The story of the love affair between FDR and his distant cousin Margaret Stuckley, centered around the
weekend in 1939 when the King and Queen of the United Kingdom visited upstate New York.
Franklin D. Roosevelt, played by Bill Murray.
Daisy, played by Laura Linney.
Bertie, played by Samuel West.
Queen Elizabeth, played by Olivia Colman.
Eleanor Roosevelt, played by Olivia Williams.
Missy, played by Elizabeth Marvel.
Hyde Park on Hudson is a 2012 historical drama film directed by Roger Michell.
The film stars Bill Murray as Franklin D.
Roosevelt, Samuel West as King George VI, Olivia Colman as his wife Queen Elizabeth and Laura
Linney as Margaret "Daisy" Suckley, a cousin and childhood friend of the President.
It was based on Suckley's private journals and diaries, discovered after her death and fictionally dramatizes her close
relationship with Roosevelt and the 1939 visit of King George VI and Queen Elizabeth to Roosevelt's home.
The film explores themes of queen, franklin delano
roosevelt, park, new york state, hyde park.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.